Guide to the Board of Trustees Records, 1860-ongoing UA.02.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke University Unprocessed Materials, 1959-2004
  - Meeting Files, 1959-2004
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, October 6, 2000-February 24, 2001, Accession Number A2002-79 (Box 69)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 6, 2001-June 15, 2001, Accession Number A2002-79 (Box 70)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 24, 2001-February 23, 2002, Accession Number A2003-32 (Box 71)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 5, 2002-June 14, 2002, Accession Number A2003-32 (Box 72)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 23, 2002-March 1, 2003, Accession Number A2004-42 (Box 73)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 11, 2003-June 20, 2003, Accession Number A2004-42 (Box 74)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 29, 2003-February 27-28, 2004, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 92)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 2, 2004-June 18, 2004, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 93)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Minutes (Box 95)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Board of Trustees materials are restricted until 2057.
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Summary of Action (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Agenda and Schedule of Events (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Cover Letters and Memorandums (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Materials Distributed at Meeting (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Attendee List/Seating Chart (Box 95)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting September 28-29, 2007 (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Standing Committee Agendas (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Audit Committee Meeting (Box 95)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (BOARD) Items taken to copy center (Box 95)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting September 28-29, 2007 Extra Copy (Box 95)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting September 28-29, 2007 Office Copy (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Minutes (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Summary of Action (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Agenda (Box 95)
    - Executive Committee Meeting November 9, 2007 Office Copy (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Cover Letters and Memorandums (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Materials Distributed at Meeting (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Attendee List/Seating Chart (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Office Copy (Box 95)
    - November 9, 2007 (EXECUTIVE) Items Taken to Copy Center (Box 95)
    - Executive Committee Meeting November 9, 2007 Extra Copy (Box 95)
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Minutes (Box 95)
      Board of Trustees materials are restricted until 2058.
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Cover Letters/Cancelation of Meeting (Box 95)
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Summary of Action (Box 95)
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Agendas (Box 95)
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Cover Letters and Memorandums (Box 95)
    - January 18, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Appendices (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Minutes (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Summary of Action (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Agenda and Schedule of Events (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Materials Distributed at meeting (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Attendee List/Seating Chart (Box 95)
    - Governance Report 2008 (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Standing Committee Agendas (Box 95)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Materials (Box 96)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Audit Committee Meeting (Box 96)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Items Taken to copy center (Box 96)
    - February 29-March 1, 2008 (BOARD) Appendices (Box 96)
    - March 28, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Summary of Action (Box 96)
    - March 28, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Materials Distributed at Meeting (Box 96)
    - March 28, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Attendee List, Seating Chart (Box 96)
    - March 28, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Appendices (Box 96)
    - December 5-6, 2008 (BOARD) Summary of Action (Box 96)
    - December 5-6, 2008 (BOARD) Attendence List/Seating Chart (Box 96)
    - December 5-6, 2008 (BOARD) Office Copy (Box 96)
    - October EC 2008 (Box 96)
    - October 3-4, 2008 (BOARD) Summary of Action (Box 96)
    - October 3-4, 2008 (BOARD) Attendee List, Seating Chart (Box 96)
    - October 3-4, 2008 (BOARD) Office Copy (Box 96)
    - September 5, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Agenda (Box 96)
    - September 5, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Cover Letter and Memorandums (Box 96)
    - September 5, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Materials distributed at meeting (Box 96)
    - September 5, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Attendee List/Seating Chart (Box 96)
    - September 5, 2008 (EXECUTIVE) Office Copy (Box 96)
    - Annual Reports, 2008 (Box 96)
    - Campus Master Plan and Action Plan of May 2000, Exhibit A Board of Trustees Meeting, December 12, 2000 (Box 97)
    - Campus Planning Studies, Exhibit A Board of Trustees Meeting, September 25-26, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Committee Files, 1917-1997, bulk circa 1960-1997
    The Committee Files subseries has materials related to various committees composed of Board of Trustees members. Materials are arranged in alphabetical order.
    - Academic Affairs Committee records, February 23, 1990-May 10, 1991, Accession Number A91-88 (Box 75)
    - Buildings and Ground Committee Records, circa 1977-1984 (Box 76)
    - Buildings and Grounds Committee Records, December 5, 1997, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 93)
    - Business and Finance Committee Records, 1988-1989, Accession Number A89-39 (Box 77)
    - Business and Finance Committee Records, 1990-1995, Accession Number A97-26 (Box 78)
    - Business and Finance Committee Records, September 26, 1997-December 5, 1997, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 93)
    - Committee for the Duke University Health System Records, April 1997-May 1997, Accession Number A2000-41 (Box 79)
    - Committee for the Duke University Health System Records, November 6, 1997-December 4, 1997, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 93)
    - Student Affairs Trustee Committee Records, September 26, 1997-December 5, 1997, Accession Number UA2006-0014 (Box 93)
    - Committee files and subject files, circa 1917-1995, Accession Numbers A96-16, A96-15, A96-94, A97-54 (Box 80)
  - Other Materials, 1948-2004
    The Other Materials subseries contains reports, subject files, trustee biographical information, retreat materials, and other papers related to the Board of Trustees. These boxes are arranged in alphabetical order.
    - Board of Trustees Retreat materials, February 1996, Accession Number A2002-85 (Box 81)
    - Boards of Visitors Records, 1963-1987, Accession Numbers A92-56, A92-55 (Box 82)
    - Chancellor for Health Affairs Search records, 2003-2004, Accession Number A2004-32 (Box 83)
    - Remarks on May 6, 1994 meeting and Trustee manual (Box 84)
    - Reports, 1948-1972 (Box 85)
    - Reports, circa 1972-1988, Accession Number A94-96 (Box 86)
    - Reports, subject files, and Executive Committee exhibits, 1973-1999, Accession Numbers A2000-39, A2000-40 (Box 87)
    - Residential Program Feasibility Report, KTH, 1999, Accession Number A2000-39 (Box 88)
    - Subject files, circa 1962-1993, Accession Number A94-82 (Box 89)
    - Subject files, 1975-1989, Accession Number A92-55 (Box 90)
    - Trustee Biographical Information and other correspondence, circa 1972-1995, Accession Number A95-25 (Box 91)
    - Trustee Biographical Information and other correspondence, circa 1972-1995, Accession Number A95-25 (Box 91)